# Saurabh Dhananjay Jadhav

214-940-2672 | saurabh.iadhav@utdallas.edu | linkedin.com/in/iadhav-saurabh/ | https://sau-di.github.io/ | Dallas, TX

### **SUMMARY**

Passionate product management professional with 2 years of experience in customer interviews, product requirements, market research, road mapping, prototyping, and testing. Seeking a product management role to drive innovation and deliver successful products for the organization.

### **EDUCATION**

The University of Texas at Dallas, Dallas, TX; M.S. in Business Analytics Mumbai University, Mumbai, India; Bachelor of Engineering – Electronics

May 2023

May 2018

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Charles River Development(A State Street Company- Fintech)

**Product Management Intern** 

Dallas, TX(Remote) May 2022 – August 2022

- Designed mockups, prototypes, and product requirement documents for web-based software that displayed benchmark information, aiding investment managers in managing investments worth \$36 trillion
- Engineered web application for the Operations team to manage over \$50 million in client financials and benchmark data, utilizing mockups, prototypes, and product requirements and designing the application's data architecture

# Renegade Insurance (US-based Series-B funded Insurtech Company)

Mumbai, India(Remote)

**Associate Product Manager** 

October 2020 – July 2021

- Steered product for a channel partnership vertical driving insurance leads from the point of sale of home loan origination and reaching \$100k premium sales within 4 months; Led a cross-functional team of 6 (Devs, UX, QA)
- Administered the complete product lifecycle from product vision to product delivery, encompassing ideation, user research, road mapping, writing user stories, owning backlog, prototyping, and testing
- Analyzed usage data using tools like Power BI, Excel, and Google Analytics, determining success metrics and KPIs to identify areas for improvement
- Conducted 20+ user interviews to gain insights into customer pain points and implemented enhancements to ensure an excellent user experience, which led to an increase in users by 21%

#### Renegade Insurance

Mumbai, India(Remote)

Associate Product Manager Intern

July 2020 - September 2020

- Led MVP development of software for sharing homeowners' insurance leads to an insurance agent, onboarding 10
  users
- Implemented agile ideation to reduce sprint gaps and cut feature release time by 40%

tag8
Business Analyst Intern

Mumbai, India

5 Taly St Intern

July 2019 – February 2020

- Researched and wrote a product requirement document for feedback software for 12,000+ Automated Teller
   Machines in India for a leading bank
- Maintained Power BI dashboards to provide actionable insights for bank management

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Languages & Tools: Jira, Azure DevOps, Figma, Power BI, Microsoft Suite, Adobe Analytics, MySQL, Looker
- Industry Skills: UI/UX Research, Customer Interviews, Strategy, Agile, Wireframing, A/B Testing

### **PROJECTS**

## Lyft Case Study for New City

January 2023

- Developed an optimized pricing strategy for Lyft, which increased ride revenue by 55% for a route in a new city
- Analyzed market trends to identify key drivers of growth, which reduced CAC for new drivers and riders by an average of 38%

# UI Redesign for Quora and E-learning

April 2022

- Improved Quora UI by removing redundant information and simplifying the remaining content
- Streamlined the eLearning platform's UI by creating subject-specific boxes with overall grades, reducing homepage information, and adding an exam-related updates tab